

+6282321892265

adeirmayantiefendy@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ade-irmayanti-5969a7164/

2 Bandung, Indonesia

Ade IrmayantiPHP Web Programmer

PROFESIONAL SUMMARY

I am a graduate of informatics engineering at Widyatama Indonesia University who masters the PHP programming language, CSS, Bootstrap, and MySQL database and can master excel formulas. Familiar with Visual Basic, C++, Java Netbeans, and Oracle Database. Use the Figma platform to create UI/UX designs and prototype projects. Has more than four years of working experience in developing web-based applications in the textile industry, leadership skills,

WORK EXPERIENCE

.....

working with teams, working under pressure, and being able to adapt to new environments.

Python Web Programmer, PT. INTI - Bandung, Indonesia

July 2017 - September 2017

- Gathered user requirements through data modeling, system analysis, design and compiled results into technical spesifications.
- Create tour and travel websites to provide services for travelers who want to travel to find tourist destinations easily and effectively.

PHP Web Programmer, PT. Kahatex Cijerah - Bandung, Indonesia

July 2018 - Present

- Gathered user requirements through data modeling, system analysis, design and compiled results into technical spesifications.
- Gathered and evaluated the technical requirements for each site to produce the best code.
- Improved coding of Javascript and bootstrap to enhance user experience and functionally.
- Create a website-based application program using php to assist employee performance in recording data on the availability of production raw materials.
- Create a website-based application to order production raw materials from the warehouse to the production department.
- Create a web-based application to record stock of raw material warehouse inventory using QR as data input.

EDUCATION

.....

Informatics Engineering, 3.62 GPA September 2018 - Mei 2022 Widyatama University, Bandung Indonesai - Bachelor of Computer

CERTIFICATES

ORACLE Academy 2019
TOEFL EPT SCORES 500 2021

SKILLS

.....

Microsoft Office	Advanced	Leadership	Advanced
PHP	Advanced	MySQL	Advanced
Javascript	Advanced	Bootstrap	Intermediate
Python	Intermediate	Visual Basic	Intermediate